ILGWU Association Agreements, Out-of-Business Contracts 5780/145
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Philadelphia Blouse and Dress Contractors Association, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1954-1957 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Amended 4/67
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Amended 3/68
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1959-1962 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1958 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1935-1938 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Covered Button, Buckle and Belt Association (Philadelphia), 1979-1979 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia) (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Amended 9/61
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Amended 1/1961
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1945-1947 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Amended 2/67
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Pleaters, Stitchers, Embroiderers Association (Philadelphia), 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1947-1949 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Artificial Flower Manufacturers Board of Trade, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1949-1952 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1947-1949 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1945-1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Associated Manufacturers Tubular Piping and Trimming, Inc. (NYC), 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1953-1955 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1945-1947 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Association of Men's Belt Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC), 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Covered Button and Buckle Creators, Inc. (NYC), 1936-1937 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Covered Button and Buckle Creators, Inc. (NYC), 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Covered Button and Buckle Creators, Inc. (NYC), 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1950-1953 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1948-1950 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1944-1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1942-1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1940-1942 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Covered Button Association of New York, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Hand Covered Buckle and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Hand Covered Buckle and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Hand Covered Buckle and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Hand Covered Buckle and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Hand Covered Buckle and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1948-1950 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1950-1953 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1953 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Hand Loom Embroidery Association, Inc. (NYC), 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1950-1953 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Handbag Contractors
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1949-1952 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1947-1949 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1945-1947 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Association, Inc. (NYC), 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- National Association of Women's Belt Manufacturers Inc (NYC) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- United Ladies Belt Manufacturers (prior name), 1935-1937 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- United Ladies Belt Manufacturers (prior name), 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- United Ladies Belt Manufacturers (prior name), 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- United Ladies Belt Manufacturers (prior name), 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- National Association of Women's Belt Manufacturers, 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- National Association of Women's Belt Manufacturers, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National Association of Women's Belt Manufacturers, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National Association of Women's Belt Manufacturers, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National Association of Women's Belt Manufacturers, 1955-1958 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National Association of Women's Belt Manufacturers, 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National Association of Women's Belt Manufacturers, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National Association of Women's Belt Manufacturers, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, Inc. (NYC) (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Women's Apparel Shoulder Pad Assoc. (prior name), 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Women's Apparel Shoulder Pad Assoc. (prior name), 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Women's Apparel Shoulder Pad Assoc. (prior name), 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Women's Apparel Shoulder Pad Assoc. (prior name), 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Women's Apparel Shoulder Pad Assoc. (prior name), 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Standard agreement, same as Association
- Women's Apparel Shoulder Pad Assoc. (prior name), 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Women's Apparel Shoulder Pad Assoc. (prior name), 1951 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1988-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Association of Shoulder Pad Manufacturers, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Buttonhole Manufacturers Association (NYC), 1940-1942 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- National Buttonhole Manufacturers Association (NYC), 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  New name: Association of Piped Buttonhole Manufacturers
- National Buttonhole Manufacturers Association (NYC), 1948-1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- National Buttonhole Manufacturers Association (NYC), 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- National Buttonhole Manufacturers Association (NYC), 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- National Buttonhole Manufacturers Association (NYC), 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- National Buttonhole Manufacturers Association (NYC), 1944-1946 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1941 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  amend 1941
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1940-1942 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  amend 1940-1942
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1939-1940 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1948-1950 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1956-1960 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1952-1954 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1943 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1942-1944 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1951 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1988-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- National Women's Neckwear and Scarf Association (NYC), 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Uniform Manufacturers Exchange, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Uniform Manufacturers Exchange, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Uniform Manufacturers Exchange, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Uniform Manufacturers Exchange, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Uniform Manufacturers Exchange, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Uniform Manufacturers Exchange, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Ladies Apparel Retailers Guild (NYC) alterations, 1934-1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Repeated Amendments & Extensions
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Amended 11/1951
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA), 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA), 1956-1959 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA), 1948-1953 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA), 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Amended 2/1951
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA), 1943-1948 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Seattle Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Amended 7/22/49
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA), 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA), 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Pacific Northwest Association of Needlecraft Manufacturers (Seattle, WA), 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Seattle Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Seattle Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Amended 7/1/49
- Seattle Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1957-1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Seattle Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Seattle Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1953-1957 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- L' Association Des Manufacturers du Vetement Pour Enfants De Montreal, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- L' Association Des Manufacturers du Vetement Pour Enfants De Montreal, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- L' Association Des Manufacturers du Vetement Pour Enfants De Montreal, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- L' Association Des Manufacturers du Vetement Pour Enfants De Montreal, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- L' Association Des Manufacturers du Vetement Pour Enfants De Montreal, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Association of Manufacturers of Cloaks, Suits and Ladies' Garments of Montreal (commonly called the "Manufacturers' Council"), 1937-1940 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Association of Manufacturers of Cloaks, Suits and Ladies' Garments of Montreal (commonly called the "Manufacturers' Council"), 1943 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  award 1943
- Association of Manufacturers of Cloaks, Suits and Ladies' Garments of Montreal (commonly called the "Manufacturers' Council"), 1942-1945 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Association of Manufacturers of Cloaks, Suits and Ladies' Garments of Montreal (commonly called the "Manufacturers' Council"), 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Association of Manufacturers of Cloaks, Suits and Ladies' Garments of Montreal (commonly called the "Manufacturers' Council"), 1919-1920 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Association of Manufacturers of Cloaks, Suits and Ladies' Garments of Montreal (commonly called the "Manufacturers' Council"), 1935-1937 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Association of Manufacturers of Cloaks, Suits and Ladies' Garments of Montreal (commonly called the "Manufacturers' Council"), 1930-1932 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Manufacturers Council of the Ladies Cloak and Suit Industry of the Province of Quebec, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)